<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Lin Han&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://lhan.quest/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Lin Han&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lhan.quest/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Yabai - Tiling Window Manager for MacOS</title>
      <link>https://lhan.quest/post/yabai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lhan.quest/post/yabai/</guid>
      <description>Why and how I choose to use yabai and how I configure it (skip to configurations if that&amp;rsquo;s what you&amp;rsquo;re looking for).
The reason for me to use Tiling Window Manager on MacOS is simple:
It&amp;rsquo;s cool
MacOS default window management is so bad
I can use keyboard for everything as much as I can
Admit it or not, making it possible to keep hands on keyboard as much as possible is a way to improve your workflow efficiency - more shortcuts, faster context switching, and less time wasted on finding your cursor and clicking here and there (espcially when you have to use bluetooth mouse sometimes, yes it&amp;rsquo;s Logitech MX master and I really hate it).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Ubuntu Configuration</title>
      <link>https://lhan.quest/post/ubuntu-configs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lhan.quest/post/ubuntu-configs/</guid>
      <description>This article aims to backup my configuration on Ubuntu.
This may also helps you to make Ubuntu elegant for use.
Shell Terminator Terminator is a terminal emulator allows multiple custom configurations, including separating windows, lots of shortcuts, and etc.
Install sudo apt-get update sudo apt-get install terminator Another great choice is Guake. But you can set Terminator behave the same way as Guake by shortcuts.
zsh and oh-my-zsh Previously I use fish, which is super powerful in auto-suggestion and syntax-highlighting, and it&amp;rsquo;s easy to use even without complicated configuration.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
